lawfuel.com 2015-04-18

# Privacy Policy - LawFuel

**Privacy Policy**

This website (the “Website”) provides users with access to LawFuel’s publishing services. Our policies with regard to data collection and use of personal information of users and visitors to the Website are set forth in this statement (“Policy”). By using this Website, you signify your acceptance of this Policy.

**Information Collection and Used by LawFuel**

LawFuel collects users’ e-mail address and profession to authenticate users and to send notifications to those users relating to the LawFuel service. We may also use a user’s email address to send updates, a newsletter or news or information regarding the service if you opt in to receive these emails during registration.

LawFuel may also log IP addresses and aggregates non-personally identifiable user data and browser type from users and visitors to the Website. This data is used to manage the website, track usage and improve the website services. User IP addresses are recorded for security and monitoring purposes. This data is gathered using cookies and other similar technologies to customize the user’s experience and also provide us with information about how visitors use the Website.

**Email Choice/Opt-out**

Users who opt in to receive emails during their use of LawFuel may choose to no longer receive e-mail updates and newsletters by selecting the “opt-out of future email” option in the email they receive from Linex or in their Linex account management screen.  
**Security**

LawFuel takes reasonable precautions to ensure that user information is kept private. We restrict access to user information to those individuals who reasonably need access to perform their job functions, such as our third party email service, customer service personnel and technical staff. However, please note that no method of transmitting or storing data is completely secure and we cannot guarantee the security of user information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of user information at any time.

If you have reason to believe that your interaction with us is no longer secure, you must immediately notify us of the problem by contacting us at _**lawfuel@gmail.com**_. In the unlikely event that we believe that the security of your user information in our possession or control may have been compromised, we may seek to notify you of that development and, if so, will endeavour to do so as promptly as practicable under the circumstances.

**Sharing and Disclosure of Information**

Except as otherwise described in this privacy statement, LawFuel will not disclose personal information to any third party unless we believe that disclosure is necessary to: (1) comply with applicable laws; (2) respond to governmental inquiries or requests; (3) comply with valid legal process; (4) protect the rights, privacy, safety or property of LawFuel , Website visitors or the public; (5) permit us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain; and (6) enforce our Terms & Conditions of Use.

In the event that LawFuel is acquired by or merged with a third-party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information that we have collected on or through this Website as part of that merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control.

**Links to Other Websites**

This Website contains links to other websites. The operator of such other websites may collect information about you, including through cookies or other technologies. If you link to another site, you will leave this Website and this Policy will not apply to your use of and activity on those other sites. We encourage you to read the legal notices posted on those sites, including their privacy policies. We shall have no responsibility or liability for your visitation to, and the data collection and use practices of, such other sites. This Policy applies solely to the information collected in connection with your use of this Website and does not apply to any practices conducted offline or in connection with any other websites.

**Changes in Our Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to change this Policy at any time. Please refer to the date at the top of this page to determine when this Policy was last revised. Any changes to our privacy policy will become effective upon posting of the revised policy on the Website. By continuing to use the Website following such changes, you will be deemed to have agreed to such changes. If you do not agree with the terms of this Policy, as it may be amended from time to time, in whole or part, please do not continue using this Website.

**Contacting LawFuel**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, your dealings with this site, or if you would like to change any of the information you have provided to us, please contact us at: **lawfuel@gmail.com**
